Your favorite pain in the neck is about to bite your funny bone!
Love at First Bite is a romance, comedy, horror film directed by Stan Dragoti.
Dracula and Renfield relocate to '70s era New York in search of Cindy
Sondheim, the reincarnation of Dracula's one true love, Mina Harker.
"Trouble adjusting" is a wild understatement for the Count as he battles Cindy's psychiatrist,
Jeffrey Rosenberg, a descendant of Van Helsing, who may be in love with Cindy too.
Count Vladimir Dracula, played by George Hamilton.
Cindy Sondheim, played by Susan Saint James.
Dr. Jeffery Rosenberg / Van Helsing, played by Richard Benjamin.
Lieutenant Ferguson NYPD, played by Dick Shawn.
Mr. Renfield, played by Arte Johnson.
Reverend Mike, played by Sherman Hemsley.
Love at First Bite is a 1979 American comedy horror film directed by Stan Dragoti and
written by Robert Kaufman, using characters originally created by Bram Stoker.
It stars George Hamilton, Susan Saint James, Richard Benjamin, and Arte Johnson.
The film's plot details the misadventures of Count Dracula in New York City while pursuing the object of his romantic desires, fashion model Cindy Sondheim,
only to find himself a fish out of water in the Big Apple and having to contend with the inimical attentions of Cindy's would-be boyfriend.
The original music score was composed by Charles Bernstein.
The film's tagline is: "Your favorite pain in the neck is about to bite your funny bone!"  An
earlier version of the script by director Richard Rush was titled Dracula Sucks Again.
The film explores themes of new york city, vampire, coffin, romcom, spoof.
The tone is dark and lighthearted and emotional.